Stern, Robert, Canadian Postal Study Archives Data Files /4050
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Robert Stern Canadian Postal Study Archives Data Files
1974-1976
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Stern, Robert
/4050
6 cubic feet
6 linear ft.
Records (documents).
3085012
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 13, 2016
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, February 22, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4102: William Foote Whyte Additional Papers /4157: ILR School Department of Organizational Behavior Records /4231: Robert Stern Papers /4297: ILR School Biography Files
Stern, Robert N.,1948-; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations --Faculty.
3085012
- British Colombia A-V, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Vancouver, British Colombia, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Victoria, B.C., 1975 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Williams Lake, B.C., 1975 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Calgary Alberta, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Edmonton - Alberta, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Fort McMurray, Alberta, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Lethbridge Alberta, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Medicine Hat, Alberta, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Regina, Sask., 1975 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Moose Jay, Sask, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Saskatoon Sask., 1975 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Winnipeg - Manitoba, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Brandon, Winnipeg, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Agincourt, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Arnprior, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Aurora, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Barrie, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Bowmansville, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Bradford, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Brantford, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Brampton, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Brighton, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Brockville, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Burks Falls Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Burlington, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Cambridge, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Chatham, Ontario (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Clinton, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Coburg, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Collingwood, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Don Mills, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Dresden, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Dryden, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Dundas, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Etobicoke, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Exeter, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Fergus, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Freeholder, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Gwelph, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Hamilton, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Huntsville, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Islington, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Kenora, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Kincardine, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Kingsville, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Kingston, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Kirkland Lake, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Kitchener, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Leaside, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Lincoln, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Trenton, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Vankleek, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Welland, Port, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- West Hill, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Willowdale, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Windsor, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Wingham, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Woodbridge, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Woodstock, Ingersoll, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Mississauga, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Morrisburg, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 62)
- Mount Forest, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 63)
- Napanee, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 64)
- New, Hamburg, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 65)
- New Liskeard, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 66)
- Niagara Falls, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 67)
- North Bay, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 68)
- Oakville, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 69)
- Orillia, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 70)
- Oshawa, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 71)
- London, Ontario, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 72)
- Ottawa, Ontario, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Ottawa, Ontario, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Ottawa, Ontario, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Owen Sound, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Pembroke, Ontario, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Peterborough, Ontario, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Pickering, Ontario, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Port Credit, Ontario, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Port Hope, Ontario, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Prescott, Ontario, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Renfrew, Ontario, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Richmond Hill, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Sachem, Ontario, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- St. Catharines, Ontario, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- St. Clairs, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- St. Thomas Ontario, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Sarnia, Ontario, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Sault, St. Marie, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Scarborough, Ontario, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Simcoe, Ontario, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Southampton, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Stoney Creek, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Stratford, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Strathoy, Ontario, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Sudbury, Ontario, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Thunder Bay, Ontario, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Timmins, Ontario, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Tilbury, Ontario, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Toronto, Ontario, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Toronto, Ontario, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Toronto, Ontario, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Toronto, Ontario, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Toronto, Ontario, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Toronto, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous, Ontario, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Montreal, Quebec, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Mount Royal, Quebec, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Montreal, Quebec, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Montreal, Quebec, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Montreal, Quebec, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Montreal, Quebec, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Montreal, Quebec, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- St. Hyacinthe, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Sherbrooke, Quebec, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Bathurst NB, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Campbellton NB, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Fredericton NB, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Moncton, NB, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- New Castle, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- St. John NB, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Amherst NS, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Dartmouth, NS, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Halifax NS, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Kentville, NS., 1975 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- New Glasgow, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Picton, NS., 1975 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Stanstead, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Sydney, NS., 1975 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Truro, NS., 1975 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Yarmouth, NS., 1975 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Charlottetown PEI, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Pioneer PEI, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Corner Brook NF, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Corner Brook NF, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Grand Falls NF, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- St. John NF, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- New York, U.S.A., 1975 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- No Town Listed, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Whitehouse, Yukon, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Montreal Mateie, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Le Devoir, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Journal de Montreal, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  Scope and Contents
  French
- Le Seur, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- La Presse, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Bob Stern, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Le Soleil, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Le Morrelliate, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- La Tribune, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- La Dustideau, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Bob Stern and Research, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Diamonds, Matire, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Misc. (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Canada, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Canada Strike, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Postal Strike Vancouver, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Canada, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Canada, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Postal Strike Calgary Herald, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Canadian Strikes, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Canada, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Postal Strike, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- New Towns, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- 1975 Postal Strike (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Postal Strike Manuscript, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  Bound
- Verbatim Report, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Canadian Union of Postal Workers, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Canada Strike, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Toronto, Ontario, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- 1975 Postal Strike (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Misc., 1975 (Box 6, Folder 12)